{
    "user_name": "Susanna",
    "session_complete_time": "2018-12-04 19:32:53.613198",
    "session_pk": 13,
    "session_size": 6,
    "block_size": 6,
    "policy_id": 2,
    "block_data": [
        {
            "block_id": 58,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 345,
                    "question_pk": 16,
                    "question": "But I was told I couldn't ride something like that, because my blood pressure could drop and I might have blacked out.",
                    "chunk": "my blood pressure could drop ",
                    "chunk_translation": "mein Blutdruck k\u00f6nnte sinken",
                    "answer": "my blood pressure could drop",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 346,
                    "question_pk": 26,
                    "question": "I have some every morning in my tea and another shot every night with lemonade.",
                    "chunk": "in my tea ",
                    "chunk_translation": "in meinem Tee",
                    "answer": "in my tea",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 347,
                    "question_pk": 207,
                    "question": "I went to a rehearsal space alone, put it on and started creating rhythms.",
                    "chunk": "put it on ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Zieh es an",
                    "answer": "put it on",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 348,
                    "question_pk": 904,
                    "question": "Next, we had to work out the combination: blindly opening the safe by force might have hurt or suffocated the boy.",
                    "chunk": "had to work out the combination",
                    "chunk_translation": "musste die Kombination ausarbeiten",
                    "answer": "have to work out the combination",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 349,
                    "question_pk": 200,
                    "question": "As soon as I finished my treatment in 2011, I said to my prosthetist that it was time to try a peg leg so I could dance.",
                    "chunk": "finished my treatment in 2011",
                    "chunk_translation": "beendete meine Behandlung im Jahr 2011",
                    "answer": "had finished my treatment in 2011",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 350,
                    "question_pk": 1169,
                    "question": "(My own background is in communications and public relations.)",
                    "chunk": "is in communications and public relations",
                    "chunk_translation": "ist in der Kommunikation und \u00d6ffentlichkeitsarbeit",
                    "answer": "is in communications and public relations",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 59,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 351,
                    "question_pk": 446,
                    "question": "I was trying to hold it back, but the labour had begun.",
                    "chunk": "was trying to hold it back",
                    "chunk_translation": "versuchte es zur\u00fcckzuhalten",
                    "answer": "was trying to hold it back",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 352,
                    "question_pk": 468,
                    "question": "As soon as the taxi stopped, my husband ran to get help.",
                    "chunk": "as the taxi stopped",
                    "chunk_translation": "als das Taxi anhielt",
                    "answer": "as the taxi stopped",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 353,
                    "question_pk": 324,
                    "question": "It was horrible, lying there not being able to move, nobody knowing where I was or having any way of finding me.",
                    "chunk": "having any way of finding me",
                    "chunk_translation": "Irgendeine M\u00f6glichkeit, mich zu finden",
                    "answer": "having any way of finding me",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 354,
                    "question_pk": 496,
                    "question": "About 10 minutes after the birth, while I was still in the medical centre and we were waiting for the ambulance, my husband scrubbed down the taxi.",
                    "chunk": "the medical centre ",
                    "chunk_translation": "das medizinische Zentrum",
                    "answer": "the medical centre",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 355,
                    "question_pk": 13,
                    "question": "I didn't choose to go on that  it was a bit too gentle.",
                    "chunk": "was a bit too gentle",
                    "chunk_translation": "war ein bisschen zu sanft",
                    "answer": "was a bit too gentle",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 356,
                    "question_pk": 362,
                    "question": "After about 15 minutes, by pure chance, one of the boys hit the back of my leg.",
                    "chunk": "the back of my leg",
                    "chunk_translation": "die R\u00fcckseite meines Beines",
                    "answer": "the back of my leg",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 60,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 357,
                    "question_pk": 447,
                    "question": "I was trying to hold it back, but the labour had begun.",
                    "chunk": "trying to hold it back",
                    "chunk_translation": "versuchen, es zur\u00fcckzuhalten",
                    "answer": "trying to hold it back",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 358,
                    "question_pk": 262,
                    "question": "Since losing my leg, I've worked on different musicals, celebrating the fact that I'm an amputee.",
                    "chunk": "Since losing my leg",
                    "chunk_translation": "Seit meinem Bein verlieren",
                    "answer": "Since losing my leg",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 359,
                    "question_pk": 786,
                    "question": "I felt very attached to the brave pair and found it quite hard to leave them.",
                    "chunk": "found it quite hard to leave them",
                    "chunk_translation": "fand es ziemlich schwer, sie zu verlassen",
                    "answer": "found it quite hard to leave them",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 360,
                    "question_pk": 91,
                    "question": "That was an achievement  for me or my mother, I'm not sure.",
                    "chunk": "an achievement  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "eine Errungenschaft",
                    "answer": "an achievment",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 361,
                    "question_pk": 223,
                    "question": "There is a different technique; with a real foot you've got a heel and toe, and you can make different sounds and rhythms.",
                    "chunk": "is a different technique",
                    "chunk_translation": "ist eine andere Technik",
                    "answer": "is a different technique",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 362,
                    "question_pk": 718,
                    "question": "But there was no movement so, despite knowing nothing about sheep, I said I was going to help.",
                    "chunk": "despite knowing nothing about sheep",
                    "chunk_translation": "obwohl ich nichts \u00fcber Schafe wei\u00df",
                    "answer": "despite knowing nothing about sheep",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 61,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 363,
                    "question_pk": 549,
                    "question": "Probably, but I do think that this way it's a nice story to remember.",
                    "chunk": "do think that this way ",
                    "chunk_translation": "denke das so",
                    "answer": "think doing this that way",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 364,
                    "question_pk": 467,
                    "question": "As soon as the taxi stopped, my husband ran to get help.",
                    "chunk": "As soon as the taxi stopped",
                    "chunk_translation": "Sobald das Taxi anhielt",
                    "answer": "As soon as the taxi stopped",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 365,
                    "question_pk": 330,
                    "question": "The avalanche covered the area of a football pitch, so it was a needle-in-a-haystack scenario.",
                    "chunk": "the area of a football pitch",
                    "chunk_translation": "die Fl\u00e4che eines Fu\u00dfballfeldes",
                    "answer": "the area of a football pitch",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 366,
                    "question_pk": 938,
                    "question": "By this time we had worked out a way to reduce the 10-minute pause between punching in codes to just one minute, so quickly we tried them all.",
                    "chunk": "to just one minute",
                    "chunk_translation": "zu einer Minute",
                    "answer": "to just one minute",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 367,
                    "question_pk": 452,
                    "question": "He was telling me all about his wife's birthing experiences, and advising me on how I should breathe.",
                    "chunk": "how I should breathe",
                    "chunk_translation": "wie ich atmen sollte",
                    "answer": "how I should breathe",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 368,
                    "question_pk": 69,
                    "question": "It turned out that I was probably the oldest person in the world to do it, and the video clip of me was very popular.",
                    "chunk": "the video clip of me was very popular",
                    "chunk_translation": "Der Videoclip von mir war sehr beliebt",
                    "answer": "the video clip of me was very popular",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 62,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 369,
                    "question_pk": 448,
                    "question": "I was trying to hold it back, but the labour had begun.",
                    "chunk": "to hold it back",
                    "chunk_translation": "um es zur\u00fcckzuhalten",
                    "answer": "to hold it back",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 370,
                    "question_pk": 158,
                    "question": "It was during a production in 2009 at university, where I was studying musical theatre, that I started to feel pain in my right leg.",
                    "chunk": "during a production in 2009 ",
                    "chunk_translation": "w\u00e4hrend einer Produktion im Jahr 2009",
                    "answer": "during a production in 2009",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 371,
                    "question_pk": 329,
                    "question": "The avalanche covered the area of a football pitch, so it was a needle-in-a-haystack scenario.",
                    "chunk": "covered the area of a football pitch",
                    "chunk_translation": "umfasste die Fl\u00e4che eines Fu\u00dfballfeldes",
                    "answer": "covered the area of a football pitch",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 372,
                    "question_pk": 593,
                    "question": "She wanted to show me I was stupid.",
                    "chunk": "wanted to show me ",
                    "chunk_translation": "wollte es mir zeigen",
                    "answer": "wanted to show me",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 373,
                    "question_pk": 637,
                    "question": "I became quite senior, working in war zones.",
                    "chunk": "working in war zones",
                    "chunk_translation": "in Kriegsgebieten arbeiten",
                    "answer": "working in war zones",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 374,
                    "question_pk": 768,
                    "question": "When the lamb was breathing and more robust, I tried to stand it up, but because it had been in the birthing position for so long, its legs kept curling under.",
                    "chunk": "breathing and more robust",
                    "chunk_translation": "atmen und robuster",
                    "answer": "breathing and more robust",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 63,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 375,
                    "question_pk": 450,
                    "question": "I was trying to hold it back, but the labour had begun.",
                    "chunk": "I was trying to hold it back",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich habe versucht, es zur\u00fcckzuhalten",
                    "answer": "I was trying to hold it back",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 376,
                    "question_pk": 318,
                    "question": "My phone was going off, but my arms were trapped so I couldn't answer.",
                    "chunk": "My phone was going off",
                    "chunk_translation": "Mein Telefon ging ab",
                    "answer": "My phone was going off",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 377,
                    "question_pk": 482,
                    "question": "The only thing between me and the car seat was a maternity pad.",
                    "chunk": "The only thing ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Das einzige",
                    "answer": "The only thing",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 378,
                    "question_pk": 931,
                    "question": "He gave us six birth dates and anniversaries to try.",
                    "chunk": "gave us six birth dates ",
                    "chunk_translation": "gab uns sechs Geburtsdaten",
                    "answer": "gave us six birth dates",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 379,
                    "question_pk": 621,
                    "question": "I was a great soldier  I got my green beret  but I couldn't write a report.",
                    "chunk": "a great soldier  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "ein gro\u00dfer Soldat",
                    "answer": "a great soldier",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 380,
                    "question_pk": 947,
                    "question": "It was dangerous, but I was confident that we could get him out.",
                    "chunk": "was confident that we could get him out",
                    "chunk_translation": "war zuversichtlich, dass wir ihn rausholen k\u00f6nnten",
                    "answer": "was confident that we could get him out",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}